let quiz=[
    {
      question: "The two ways to arrange multiple windows on the desktop are :",
      option: [
           "cascade and tile",
           "drag and drop",
           "point and click",
           "minimize and maximize",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is a programming language for creating special programs like applets :",
      option: [
           "Java",
           "Cable",
           "Domain name",
           "Net",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is true about Assembly Language :",
      option: [
           "It is an object oriented programming language",
           "It is a high-level programming language",
           "It is a low-level programming language",
           "It is a language for assembling computers",
      ],
       answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "ER Diagram in DBMS is a graphical method used to represent :",
      option: [
           "Primary key and candidate key",
           "Entity class and their relationships",
           "Objects and methods with functions",
           "Entity class and relationship to foreign key only",
      ],
      answer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the other name for addictive manufacturing :",
      option: [
           "3-D printing",
           "2-D printing",
           "CPU assembly",
           "Memory management",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "______ is an object embedded in a web page or email, which unobtrusively(usually invisibly) allows checking that a user has accessed the content :",
      option: [
           "email",
           "virus",
           "web beacon",
           "spam",
      ],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is not an in-built software application found in MS Windows :",
      option: [
           "Paint",
           "CD Player",
           "Disk Defragmeter",
           "Volume Control",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What is that computer program called which translates one program instruction at a time into machine language :",
      option: [
           "Compiler",
           "CPU",
           "ROM",
           "Interpreter",
      ],
      answer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the overall term for creating, editing, formatting, storing, retrieving and printing a text document :",
      option: [
           "Word Processing",
           "Spreadsheet Design",
           "Web Design",
           "Database Management",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is the communication protocol that sets the standard used by every computer that accesses web based information :",
      option: [
           "XML",
           "DML",
           "HTTP",
           "HTML",
      ],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
  question: "Another Name for a logic chip is:",
  option: [
  "PROM",
  "Memory",
  "Microprocessor",
  "ROM",
  ],
  answer: 3, 
},
 {
  question: "The Number System based on 0 and 1 only is known as",
  option: [
  "Binary System",
  "Barter System",
  "Number System",
  "Hexadecimal System",
  ],
  answer: 1, 
},
 {
  question: "Which of the following is not part of the CPU ?",
  option: [
  "Primary Storage",
  "Registers",
  "Control Unit",
  "ALU",
  ],
  answer: 1, 
},
 {
  question: "Which of the following represents the fastest data transmission speed ?",
  option: [
  "Bandwidth",
  "bps",
  "gbps",
  "kbps",
  ],
  answer: 3, 
},
 {
  question: "What is the major feature of the WWW that makes it simple to learn and use?",
  option: [
  "Database Interface",
  "Graphical text Interface",
  "Graphical user Interface",
  "Point-to-Point protocol",
  ],
  answer: 3, 
},
    ]   
